(Penny:)Get in the car. Come on.
(Stuart(on phone):)All right, thanks a lot.
(Stuart(on phone):)They have one at Capital Comics.
(Bernadette:)-That's great.
-No, its not. I hate that place.
(Stuart:)Guy who owns it is a jerk.
(Stuart:)He's always making me
feel bad about myself.
(Bernadette:)That's terrible.
(Bernadette:)What's the address?
(Stuart:)You know, why don't I
just take you there?
(Stuart:)That way, I can make sure
he doesn't rip you off.
(Bernadette:)Thanks, but I don't
want you to close up.
(Bernadette:)I mean, won't you lose business?
(Bernadette:)Sorry. That was mean.
(Amy:)Penny really quit
The Cheesecake Factory?
(Penny:)-Yeah.
-So what is she doing today?
(Leonard:)I don't know. She already
thinks I don't support this,
(Leonard:)so if I call, it might look like
I'm checking up on her.
(Raj:)-Well, do you support this?
-of course I do.
(Leonard:)She's a great actress.
I'm proud she's taking this risk.
(Amy:)-That's nice.
-You bought that? Great!